

I'm an open-minded, personable, and multi-skilled individual with an extensive experience in digital products, having worked in the industry for the past 18 years in both technical and design leadership roles.

I am adaptable and self-motivated with an exceptional eye for detail, focused on creating positive and successful experiences that feel right.

Employment

Since December 2020

Lead User Experience Designer

UNRVLD Cardiff, UK Running a variety of digital projects across several industries (retail, property, travel, B2B, finance, banking, education, ...). Responsible for managing a team of user experience designers. Introducing internal process improvements from standardising user research and experimentation activities, to optimising the team's design output (e.g. design boilerplates, shared libraries, general housekeeping).

Sept 2018 - Dec 2020

Senior UX/UI Designer

Kagool Cardiff, UK Responsible on translating client business objectives into opportunities for design by running user-centred design activities, through discovery workshops and design sprints, from initial concepts to production.

Feb 2017 - Sept 2018

Senior Product Designer (Lead)

GoCompare Newport, UK Responsible for leading, managing and growing a team of Product Designers and acted as design owner and strategic partner with the technology and product leadership teams on key initiatives. Successfully introduced and lead the adoption of a design system across the business, enabling the design, production and launch of a new range of GoCompare products including GoCompare Energy and WeFlip.

Oct 2015 - Jan 2017

Web Design Manager

GoCompare Newport, UK Responsible for growing, managing and mentoring the Web Design/UX team to successfully translate concepts into leading-edge interactive experiences that successfully pushed the GoCompare brand forward.

Apr 2014 - Sept 2015

Web User Experience Designer

GoCompare Newport, UK Lead the redesign of the GoCompare key user journeys, and created a web based style-guide, to implement a usable and consistent user experience across over 20 financial products comparison journeys such as Home Insurance, Car Insurance, and Travel Insurance.

Oct 2010 - Sept 2014

Freelance Web Developer, Designer & Illustrator

Julien Decaudin Ltd London, Cardiff, UK Provided hand crafted web solutions, design identity and illustration to a wide range of clients as well as collaborations with leading UK digital agencies such as Poke, Isobar, SAS/MSLGROUP and BEAR.

Jan 2007 - Sept 2010 Senior Web Developer

SAS Responsible of integration and client training on the CMS Umbraco for

London, UK clients such as Coca-Cola, BP, Freshfields and Ernst & Young. Worked

closely with the Design team on user interface research and development.

Lead front-end and back-end development process optimization.

Feb 2005 - Aug 2006 Web Developer

Kaliop Developed and contributed to the back-end interface design of Kaliop in-

Montpellier, France house CMS. Lead the development of an e-commerce website.

Education

2001 - 2005 Masters Degree

Universite d'Avignon, France Computer Science

1999 - 2001 HND

Universite d'Aix-Marseille, France Telecommunications and Networks

Training

2019 Designing for Persuasion, Emotion & Trust

Bunnyfoot, London, UK Applying behavioural science to create digital products more likely to

result in positive interactions and conversions from customers.

2018 Fundamentals of Service Design

Bunnyfoot, London, UK Understand the fundamentals of service design thinking and how to apply

them to improve service quality across digital and physical touchpoints.

Expertise

Concept User-centred design, User testing, Design systems, Agile

Management Team management, Recruitment, OKR, Product roadmap prioritisation

Design Product design, UX design, Web design, Illustration, Graphic design

Tools Figma, Sketch, InVision, Adobe CC, Miro, Whimsical

Development HTML5, Sass, Javascript, Node.js, Vue.js, .NET, Git

Language Native French, Fluent English

Interests

Illustration, music production, photography, running, trekking, swimming

References

Available on LinkedIn